你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
欢迎收看这段视频，在这段视频中，我们将结束关于如何删除文件的讨论
And welcome to this video where we're going to be finishing off our discussion of how to delete files
以及使用命令行的目录。
and directories using the command line.
因此，在这个视频中，您将学习如何使用Ahram和MDR命令来删除文件夹。
So in this video you're going to learn how to use the Ahram and are MDR commands to delete folders.
在本视频结束时，您将了解有关删除文件所需了解的几乎所有内容
And by the end of this video you'll know pretty much everything you need to know about deleting files
以及使用命令行的文件夹。
and folders using the command line.
所以，让我们继续直截了当地谈吧。
So let's go ahead and get right into it.
好的，让我们首先在主目录中创建一个名为Del Folder的文件夹。
All right so let's start off by creating a folder in our home directory called Del folder.
因此，如果我使用mkdir命令并键入Del Folder，我们将看到我们在
So if I use the mkdir command and type Del folder we'll see that we created a new folder inside our
名为Del Folder的主目录。
home directory called Del folder.
好的。
OK.
所以我们把它移走吧。
So let's remove it.
好的，现在我们要做的就是删除它，再次使用r.m命令来使用Ahram和del
OK now all we have to do actually to remove it is use the r.m command again for use Ahram and use del
文件夹，然后按Enter键。
folder and press enter.
我们实际上得到了一个错误。
We actually get an error.
现在这是因为是的，我们将使用R.M命令，但为了让R M命令删除文件夹
Now this is because yes we will use the r.m command but in order for the R M command to remove folders
我们需要给r.m命令提供r选项，但是r选项代表递归或递归。
we need to give the r.m command the r option but the r option stands for recursive or recursively.
现在，如果您递归地删除某些内容，这意味着您将删除该内容以及其中的其他所有内容
Now if you delete something recursively that means you'll delete that thing and everything else inside
关于它的。
of it.
如果我们现在尝试这样做，我们的公羊，劈开，我们的，然后删除文件夹，OK，然后按Enter键。
So if we try that now our ram slash our and then del folder OK and press enter.
现在我们将看到Del文件夹确实已被删除。
We'll see now that Del folder has indeed been deleted.
所以让我们再做一次，再做一次，让Del Folder OK，让我们在里面做一些更多的文件夹。
So let's make it again make it again make Del folder OK and let's make some more folders inside of it.
所以我们现在要使用括号扩展。
So we're going to use brace expansion for this now.
好的。
OK.
我们可以创建make directory Del文件夹，在里面我们将创建三个名为Delete的文件夹
We can do make make directory Del folder and inside there we're going to make three folders called Delete
我是一号、二号和三号。
me one two and three.
好的。
OK.
因此，如果我按Enter键并查看戴尔文件夹，我们可以看到我们已经找到了我想要找到的销售线索
So if I press enter and take a look at Dell folder we can see we've got the lead me want to get me to
把我删掉3号。
and delete me 3.
所以这就是它的运作方式。
So that's how this works.
我们先让它让我想要进入戴尔，然后它可能也会删除我。
We made first it made me want inside of Dell for that then it may delete me too.
然后它又让我删除了3个大括号扩展。
Then it made delete me 3 comsats brace expansion again.
那么让我们在每个文件中创建一些文件。
So let's make some files inside each of those.
因此，如果我们触摸戴尔文件夹，删除我，请删除我1、2和3，然后在他们的make文件中删除
So if we touch Dell folder delete me delete me one two and three and then inside of their make file
一、二、三。
one two and three.
现在，如果我们看一看，我们可以看到并删除我的一个。
And now if we take a look we can see and delete me one.
我们有4，1，2和3，然后删除12，2和3中的我2，然后删除我3。
We've got four one two and three and delete me 2 for 1 2 and 3 and then delete me 3.
我们有12号文件，2号文件和3号文件。
We've got file 1 2 and 3.
现在，如果我们继续查看，这里有Del文件夹，我们的
So now if we if we go ahead and if we just look we've got Del folder here we've got Dell folder in our
主目录。
home directory.
现在，如果我们将RAM与删除该Del文件夹的选项一起使用，请记住递归删除某些内容
Now if we use our ram with the option to delete that Del folder remember to delete something recursively
意味着删除它和它里面的其他所有东西。
means to delete it and everything else inside of it.
因此，如果我使用带有选项的r.m，并将其指定为Delphos，则按Enter键将看到该文件夹确实
So if I use r.m with the option and give it Delphos then press enter will see that folder has indeed
已经被删除了，里面的其他东西也都被删除了。
been deleted and so has everything else inside of it.
现在，您可能会注意到一件事，当rm命令这样做时，它实际上没有为我们提供任何
Now one thing you might notice is that the r.m command when it did that it actually didn't give us any
警告。
warning.
它只是继续并删除了戴尔文件夹中的所有内容。
It just went ahead and deleted everything inside the Dell folder folder.
好的。
OK.
正因为如此，我们的公羊冲向他们的腐败是一个非常强大的命令，应该是
Now because of this our ram dash on em with the corruption is a very powerful command that should be
处理得非常小心，特别是当你开始使用星牌通配符的时候。
dealt with very carefully especially when you start using the Star wild card as well.
所有事情都可能出错，您会发现自己只是删除了所有内容，无法获取
All things can go wrong and you can find yourself just deleting everything and not being able to get
你的文件回来了，这是悲哀的时候。
your files back which is sad sad times.
例如，如果我现在继续这样做，如果我只是在我们系统上的所有内容上删除它，对吗？
So for example if I do go ahead and do that now if I just delete that on everything on our system right
现在我不打算这么做了，我在开玩笑。
now I'm not going to do it I'm joking.
所以，让论点变得更安全的一种方法，实际上是给它一个选择。
So one way to make the argument safer is actually to give it the option.
好的。
OK.
因此，该选项代表交互，这将使命令中的r交互倾斜。
So the option stands for interactive and this will make the r in command askew interactively.
是否删除每个文件。
Whether to delete each file or not.
现在我们没有戴尔文件夹了。
Now at the moment we don't have we don't have the Dell folder anymore.
因此，要同时创建戴尔文件夹并删除我的1、2和3。
So to make Dell folder and delete me one two and three all at once.
我将使用make the命令，并为其提供允许您创建完整路径的选项
I'm going to use the make the command give it the option which allows you to create an entire path and
Do Del Too和Telic Create Delete Me 1、2和3。
do Del too and Telic create delete me 1 2 and 3.
因此，如果我这样做，实际上也不会处理。
So if I do that actually not dealt too.
抱歉，戴尔文件夹。
Sorry Dell folder.
好的，我把我想要的戴尔文件夹放在里面，现在可以呼叫三个，让我们创建
OK then I get Dell folder inside there that me wanted me to do it three can call right now let's create
贝索戴尔文件夹转发劈开里面的文件，删除我一、二、三，我们要制作
the files inside Besso Dell folder forward slash delete me one two and three and we're going to make
归档1、2和3，每一个，所以每一个，我们都拿回了我们的文件。
file one two and three and so each of those and so each of those We've got our files back.
好的。
OK.
所以我们就到这里了。
So there we are.
一点也没花太长时间。
Didn't take too long at all.
顺便说一句，我们已经拿回了我们的文件。
We've got our files back by the way.
你能看到这比指着点然后点击要快得多吗？
Can you see just how much quicker this is than pointing and clicking.
我们创建了所有这些文件，甚至不需要输入从创建它们的文件夹
We created all those files without ever even needing to enter the folders which created them right from
主目录。
a home directory.
所以。
So.
太酷了。
So cool.
现在，如果我们再次尝试删除所有内容，请尝试通过给出命令R来删除DEL文件夹
So now if we tried to delete everything again try and delete Del folder by giving the command the R
和R选项。
and R options.
好的，你按什么顺序做并不重要。
OK it doesn't matter which order you do it.
所以我们给它Del文件夹，我们会看到的。
So we give it Del folder we'll see that.
现在，它请求允许我们实际删除内容，因此它说我可以进入戴尔文件夹吗。
Now it's asking permission for us to actually delete things so it's saying Can I go into Dell folder.
我们就说是吧。
Let's tell it yes.
好的。
OK.
现在它会说我可以进去删除我的一个吗？
It will now say can I go in to delete me one.
我们说好吧。
Let's say yes.
我也可以删除一个文件吗？
And can I delete a file too.
是的，可以删除4：03 3。
Yes you can can delete 4:03 three.
是的，她不能删除里面的一个。
Yes she can cannot delete for one inside.
删除我想，如果她可以，我可以删除目录，删除我一个。
Delete me want if she can can I remove the directory delete me one.
不，她可以。
Yes she can.
我可以删除任意三个吗？
Can I go into delete any three.
你看，它并没有特别按照任何顺序做，但它在做之前会问你。
You see it's not particularly doing it in any order but it's asking you before it does it.
好的。
OK.
所以说，是的，你可以这样做，你可以删除，你可以这样做。
So say yes you can do it that you can delete that you can do that.
现在让我们离开它，让我们把文件留在里面，把我也删除。
Now let's leave it let's leave file to inside delete me too.
好的。
OK.
这样你就可以删除我3了。
So you can delete delete me 3.
我也要删除了。
Going to delete me too.
不，不要删除Fall。
No don't delete fall.
是，删除5：3，赞成一人。
Yes delete 5:3 yes to the for one.
不，不要删除整个文件夹，不，不要删除文件夹，仅此而已。
No don't delete the entire folder no don't delete folder and that's it.
凯特说，如果我们查看戴尔文件夹，我们应该也会看到删除我。
Kate said if we look inside Dell folder we should see delete me too.
法尔图还没吃完。
And Faltu still leftover.
好的，这很酷，对吧。
OK so that's quite cool right.
您可以控制该命令删除的内容，但这有点单调乏味，每次都要回答是和否
You can control what the command deletes But this is kind of tedious right saying yes and no every time
是个。
it's a.
如果你有很多文件，那将会是一个巨大的麻烦。
If you had a lot of files that would that would really be a massive hassle.
幸运的是，还有另一个专门用于删除空目录的命令
So fortunately there's another command that specialized for only removing directories that are empty
现在，因为此命令只删除空目录。
now because this command only removes empty directories.
这意味着您可以告诉它删除所有内容。
This means that you can tell it to delete everything.
它将只删除实际为空的文件夹。
It will only delete the folders that are actually empty.
这意味着你永远不会不小心删除文件。
Which means you'll never delete a file accidentally.
该命令称为MDI或REMOVE DIRECTORY命令集，以查看REMOVE DIRECTORY命令
And that command is called the MDI or the remove directory command set to see the remove directory command
在行动中。
in action.
首先，让我们继续删除Dell文件夹中的所有内容，递归删除DLL文件夹和Ardell
First let's go ahead and delete everything inside Dell folder remove recursively DLL folder and Ardell
文件夹已删除。
folder has been deleted.
现在，让我们继续创建一些文件夹，因此我们将使用带有创建选项的mkdir。
Now let's go ahead and create some folders so we're going to use mkdir with the option to create.
让我们称其为戴尔文件夹，然后将其放入1到3个文件夹。
Let's call it Dell folder and then folder one to three.
这是另一种方式，你不必键入一个逗号到三个逗号。
That's another way of doing it by the way you don't have to type one comma to comma three.
你可以只做一点三。
You can just do one dot dot three.
如果我们查看Del文件夹，我们有4票对1票投3票，将10个文件夹放入1个文件夹中
And if we look in Del folder We've got 4 to 1 vote to vote 3 and as put ten folders inside folders one
两个，但不在一号文件夹里。
and two but not in folder one.
124 9：43说也要触摸Delph文件夹1，然后放入他们的文件1到10到16。
124 9:43 says to touch Delph folder folder one too and then put inside their file 1 to 10 to 16.
所以如果我们看一下里面的那个，我们现在有10个文本文件，我们在里面看这两个。
So if we look inside for the one we've now got 10 text files we look inside for the two.
我们在文件夹3中有10个文本文件。
We've got 10 text files in folder 3.
我们没有了。
We don't have any.
好的，现在我们在戴尔文件夹中有三个文件夹想要在其中包含10个文件
OK so now we've got three folders inside Dell folder folders want to follow to have 10 files in them
但是文件夹3完全是空的。
but folder 3 is completely empty.
现在，如果我试着做删除目录，我说删除目录，删除文件夹，劈开所有东西。
Now if I tried to do remove directory and I say remove directory Del folder slash everything.
好的，我们现在要说的是删除Del文件夹内的所有内容。
OK what we're saying here is delete everything inside Del folder.
删除文件夹内的空文件夹。
Delete the empty folders inside folder.
基本上，如果我这样做了，将会看到它无法删除文件夹1，因为目录不是空的
Basically if I do that will see it failed to remove folder one because the directory is not empty it
删除文件夹也失败，因为控制器不是空的，但2：56确实已被删除。
failed to remove folder too because the director is not empty but 2:56 has indeed been deleted.
所以，您要知道，如果我们只是删除戴尔文件夹的目录而不删除目录，这是不会起作用的
So just so you know this wouldn't have worked if we'd just done remove directory of Dell folder without
把星号CC放在这里我们有星号通配符。
putting the star CC we've got the star asterisk wildcard here.
如果我们刚刚移除了航天飞机站点的Delph文件夹。
If we just have removed Delph folder the shuttle site.
但是戴尔文件夹不是空的。
But Dell folders not empty.
我怎么能就这么把它删掉呢。
How can I just delete it.
我们所做的是删除空的戴尔文件夹中的所有内容。
Well what we did is we said remove everything that is inside Dell folder that is empty.
好的，所以我们必须有明星在那里，才能做到这一点。
OK so we have to have the star there to make that work.
这只是一件需要牢记在心的事情。
That's just something to bear in mind.
好的，最后一个挑战是，在上一个视频中，我们创建了一个项目文件夹，其中包含一大堆其他文件夹
OK so one final challenge in the last video we created a project folder that had a whole bunch of other
里面的文件夹，我们想要无数的文件。
folders inside we'd like a jillion files.
好的，在最后几个视频中，你一定要记住这一点。
Ok you must remember this for the last few videos.
现在我想让你们做的是，我想试着删除所有这些文件夹、目录和文件
Now what I want you to do is I want to try and delete all of those folders and directories and files
所有的东西都集中在一个命令里。
and stuff in one command.
好的，这就是你们的挑战。
OK so that's your challenge.
这是很自然的挑战，您必须尝试删除包含所有内容的整个项目文件夹
That's natural challenge you've got to try and delete the entire project folder with everything inside
因此，在一个命令中包含数千个文件。
of it all the thousands of files in one command so.
现在就上传这段视频，看看你是否能想出如何做到这一点。
Post the video now and see if you can figure out figure out how to do it.
然后再回来看看你做得怎么样。
Then come back and see how you did.
你成功了吗。
Did you manage it.
如果是这样的话。
If so.
干得好，你学得超快，超快。
Well done you learn super super quick.
所以我是这样做的。
So here is how I do it.
好的，现在我有一个名为“项目”的文件夹，写在桌面上，就是这样的移位。
OK now I have the folder was called Project write it was on the desktop such shift there.
这就是所谓的“项目”。
It's it's called Project.
因此，我们希望删除所有内容，因此不希望使用R mdr命令，因为这只会删除
So we want to delete everything so we don't want to use the R MDR command because that only deletes
空目录。
empty directories.
我们希望使用r.m命令，因为我们希望删除其中包含内容的目录。
We want to use the r.m command instead because we want to delete directories that have stuff in them.
好的，现在我们要删除项目文件夹和其中的所有内容。
OK now we want to delete the project folder and everything inside it.
所以我们需要递归删除，为此，我们将使用r选项。
So we need to delete recursively so to do that we're going to use the r option.
好的。
OK.
把所有这些放在一起，基本上意味着我们只需要递归地删除项目文件夹。
And putting it all together basically means we'll just do remove recursively the project folder.
或者，如果我在我的主目录中，像这样，我会递归地删除桌面的劈开项目。
Or if I was in my home directory like this I would remove recursively desktop's slash project.
好的，只要给出该文件夹的路径，当我按Enter键时。
OK just given the path to that folder and when I press enter.
就像施了魔法一样。
As if by magic.
然而，那里有许多文件夹，数千个文件已被删除。
However many folders there were the thousands of files have been deleted.
这是多么的史诗，所以我们关于删除文件和文件夹的讨论差不多就到此为止了
How absolutely epic is that so that'll just about wrap up our discussion of deleting files and folders
使用命令行。
using the command line.
因此，在本视频中，您了解到r.m命令需要该选项才能删除文件夹和
So in this video you learn that the r.m command needs the option in order to delete folders and the
选项代表递归删除。
option stands for recursive deleting.
因此递归删除某物意味着删除该物件及其内部的所有其他内容。
So delete something recursively means to delete that thing and everything else inside it.
这就是您在使用该选项时需要特别小心的地方，因为您最终可能会删除
And this is what you need to be especially careful when using the option because you can end up deleting
您不想知道的使其更安全的一种方法是使用R.M.
stuff that you didn't want to know one way to make that a bit safer is to use the option for the r.m
命令，该命令将允许R.m命令在执行其删除操作时是交互式的。
command which will allow the r.m command to be interactive when it does it's deleting.
这就是您可以对每个要删除的文件夹说是或不是的地方，但最好的是
So this is where you can say yes or no to each file folder being deleted but the best thing is there's
你真的没有太多可以信赖的东西。
not really much you can rely on.
删除的时候一定要小心。
Just be careful when doing your deleting.
好的。
OK.
但是，所有选项中最安全的是使用R mdr命令，该命令将只删除空的文件夹。
But the safest of all options is to use the R MDR command which will only delete folders that are empty.
因此，如果您只想稍微整理一下并删除其中没有任何内容的文件夹，您可以
So if you just want to do a bit of tidying up and delete folders that don't have anything in them you
可以使用mdr命令。
can use the MDR command.
睡觉保证你不会删除任何数据。
And rest assured that you won't delete any data.
接下来，我们将讨论如何使用
So coming up next we're going to discuss how you might copy and paste files and directories using the
命令行。
command line.
因此，我们不会砍掉我们的文件树，而是让它生长。
So instead of cutting our file tree we're going to make it grow.
好了，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
So for all that goodness I'll see you in the next video.